<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
  <items>
    <title>Archived News</title>
    <link>http://silverlight.net/blogs/news/default.aspx</link>
    <description>Silverlight News Blog</description>
    <item>
      <title>Local New Silverlight Toolkit Video</title>
      <link>http://silverlight.net/learn/videocat.aspx?cat=2#HDI2Controls</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2011 17:13:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Local Todd Miranda demonstrates how to use Silverlight Themes. Watch this and other Silverlight videos on the Learn page.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Seven New Community Gallery Entries</title>
      <link>http://silverlight.net/themes/silverlight/community/gallerydetail.aspx?cat=Silverlight2</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2011 23:43:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Local Play the Silverlight Gobang Game, practice Creating Particle Effects in Silverlight, dance with a 3D Silver Mouse, and more! Find inspiration and upload your Silverlight projects to share with the community in the Gallery. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local 16 New Silverlight Showcases</title>
      <link>http://silverlight.net/Showcase/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2011 00:38:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Local Improve your tonal memory with TwinNotes, create your own bracelets using Brighton’s Interactive Charm Builder, browse the selection of movies at Ramp DVD Store, and more in the Silverlight Showcase.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Silverlight Toolkit March 2009 Available</title>
      <link>http://silverlight.codeplex.com/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2011 05:27:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Local The Silverlight Toolkit March 2009 release is now available with more Silverlight controls, themes, samples and source code. This release includes faster charting, better Visual Studio and Expression Blendintegration and new layout and input controls, such as Accordion, TimePicker, DomainUpDown, Area Chart, Bubble Crème Theme, Twilight Blue Theme and many other new controls, themes and utilities.
      </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Download Silverlight 3 Beta today!</title>
      <link>http://silverlight.net/getstarted/silverlight3/default.aspx</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2011 05:42:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Local At MIX09 Silverlight 3 Beta was unveiled, with over 50 new features, including support for running Silverlight applications out of the browser, dramatic video performance and quality improvements, and features to improve developer productivity. Find out more and download the beta today.
      </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Nine New Community Gallery Entries</title>
      <link>http://silverlight.net/themes/silverlight/community/gallerydetail.aspx?cat=Silverlight2</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2011 00:05:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Local Monkey around with Face Monkey, watch the Basic Fluid Silverlight Animation, play Tetris or Sudoku, and more! Find inspiration and upload your Silverlight projects to share with the community in the Gallery. </description>
    </item>
   
  </items>

